<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Japan</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- String names for tabs -->
    <string name="tab_history">History</string>
    <string name="tab_places">Places</string>
    <string name="tab_food">Food</string>
    <string name="tab_secrets">Secrets</string>

    <!-- String descriptions for Places -->
    <string name="place_akihabara_station">Akihabara, also know as "Akiba," is located in the Chiyoda Ward of Tokyo and home to the Akihabara Station. The station was first opened in 1890 and today is operated by Tokyo Metro, JR East, and the Metropolitan Intercity Railway Company. Akihabara is the home of the electronic shopping district in Tokyo and contains electronic shops, casinos, restaurants, and entertainment that continues throughout the night, even during the weekdays! The station also houses many great food places from ramen to sushi to tonkatsu and more. Akihabara itself is home to otaku culuture, a place where you will find an abundance of manga and anime shops, games, electronics, and other goods.</string>
    <string name="place_ameyoko_shopping_street">Located just outside of Ueno Station, this shopping street hosts shops and vendors selling clothing goods, seafood, sweets, toys, fabrics, and much more. A quick walk from the Ueno station, Ameyoko shopping street is a great place to quickly find a bite to eat or wander through the alleys experiencing the goodness of Japanese street vendor culture. This open-air market is a must-stop-spot for tourists and visitors in the area, even if it\'s just for a few moments before you catch your next train.</string>
    <string name="place_ginza">Ginza is one of Tokyo\'s most luxurious and upbeat shopping district, packed with a variety of clothing, electronic, and home good shops and stores. The biggest and most popular name brands fill the streets of Ginza and it\'s a place you can find $100+ sushi, luxurious jewelry, and super high-fashion clothing.</string>
    <string name="place_imperial_palace">The Imperial Palace is the official residence of the Imperial Family and the Emperor of Japan. Located in the Chiyoda ward in Tokyo, the Imperial Palace is built on the land of the previous Edo Castle. Although visitors can only see parts of the castle ground, the many restored buildings and structures are a sight to behold. On New Year\'s, the castle grounds can open to where the general public can enter the main castle grounds and even see the visiting imperial family atop a balcony.</string>
    <string name="place_meiji_temple">The Meiji Shrine is dedicated to the Emperor Meiji located near Harajuku Station in Shibuya. The Shrine itself is located within the dense forestry of the park and is a ten minute walk from the entrance of the park. Many events can be taken place here in the grounds, including worships, weddings, and tourism events. At the entrance of the park is a giant Torii leading to the pathway to the shrine. Meiji shrine is the most popular shrine to visit on New Year\'s Eve, where the Japanese gatehr to pray and worship for the upcoming new year.</string>
    <string name="place_nissan_crossing">A place of excitement and innovation! Nissan Crossing is located in Ginza and is home to some amazing technology at Nissan as well as futuristic concepts and vehicles from Nissan. The wide digital interactive touch screen on the ground floor allows visitors to touch and explore the many great technologies being developed at Nissan and a virtual reality driving simulator allows car enthusiasts to experience the feeling of driving in a GTR.</string>
    <string name="place_sensoji_temple">One of Tokyo\'s oldest Buddhist temples, the Senso-Ji Temple was a temple built by two brothers for the Goddess of Mercy, Kannon. The temple was constructed in 645 and has become one of Tokyo\'s oldest and most popular temples. Nakamise, a shopping street on the temple grounds, sell a variety of goods and food.</string>
    <string name="place_shinjuku">Shinjuku is a ward in Tokyo housing the Tokyo Metropolitan Government Building. Most of this ward is comprised of office buildings and commercial buildings. Shinjuku, like most other places in Tokyo, is a busy and popular night-life ward that houses shops, restaurants, and many other tourist places.</string>
    <string name="place_tokyo_skytree">Located in Sumida, Tokyo, the Tokyo Skytree is an obervational tower, a restaurant, and a broadcasting structure and became the tallest structure tower in Japan in 2010. The Tower itself is a striking 634 meters high and is located next to Asakusa in Tokyo. Many of the shopping malls and restaurants are positioned at the base of the tower. The Tembo deck at 450 meters is used as an observational platform. For the cost of about $30-$40, tourists can visit these platforms to see the amazing skyline of Tokyo.</string>
    <string name="place_ueno_park">Ueno Park is located is a public park located near the Ueno Station. The park is famous for the many museums and galleries in Tokyo. Museums such as the National Science Museum and the Tokyo Metropolitan Art Museum reside in this park. Ueno park is also one of the popular places to view blossoming cherry blossoms in season. Being one of the most popular parks in Tokyo, visitors can be sure to experience the many great offerings it has.</string>

    <!-- String descriptions for Food -->
    <string name="food_sushi_akihabara">Sushi is plenty at Akihabara and Akihabara station is no exception. With fancy sit-down sushi to grab-and-go sushi, Akihabara station has sushi for all your needs. This particular place was a casual sit-down sushi place with a conveyor belt! Simply order what you\'d like to get on the device and in minutes, the sushi would zip past all the tables and be delivered to your table. Prices are calculated based on what sushi you pick up from the belt and there\'s unlimited matcha green tea!</string>
    <string name="food_matsuya">Matsyu is a popular Japanese breakfast and general meal chain. You can be sure to find one near and around you anywhere you visit in Tokyo. The procedure is simple! Simply order what meal you would like at the vending machine and sit down. The meal will be delivered to your table based on your ticket you received from the machine. From miso soup to raw tofu to rice and eggs and more, Matsuya is a great quick place to grab something to eat at a very small and reasonable price.</string>
    <string name="food_tokyo_tanmen_tonari">A quick order-and-eat sit-down place in Tokyo comprising a menu of ramen and many other popular Japanese dishes.</string>
    <string name="food_ueno_park_french_toast">The most amazing french toast in Tokyo. Served with ice cream. Your life is not complete without this delicious dish.</string>
    <string name="food_vie_de_france">Bakeries are immensely popular in Japan. Vie De France Bakery can be found in Akihabara station as well as many other places around Tokyo. These bakeries can be found in stations, shopping malls, and many other busy parts of Tokyo and offer a wide variety of baked goods and pastries.</string>
    <string name="food_mr_waffle">THESE ARE DELICIOUS. Nothing is more satisfying than a freshly baked and deliciously warm waffle from Mr. Waffle. From chocolate waffles to orange waffles to plenty more, these little shops provide a delicious way to consume a very popular snack in Japan. You can find these at malls, shopping districts, and sometimes even stations.</string>
    
</resources>
